Contact

clslingerrn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/chantel-slinger-174681b4 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR)

Chantel Slinger

Experienced ER nurse with personality, passion, and the ability to be a great change agent!

Vine Grove, Kentucky

Summary

Experienced nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the critical care industry. Skilled in Customer Service, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Training and Education of clinical courses and new graduates, and Critical Care Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science degree - BS focused in Registered Nursing/ Registered Nurse from University of West Florida.

Experience

SAINTS MARY & ELIZABETH HOSPITAL Emergency Room Nurse January 2020 - Present (7 months) Louisville, Kentucky, United States

Amplion Clinical Communications, Inc. Clinical Integration Specialist December 2018 - Present (1 year 8 months) Nashville, Tennessee

Aya Healthcare
2 years 11 months

Travel Registered Nurse
December 2017 - Present (2 years 8 months)

Travel Registered Nurse September 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)

Education

University of West Florida

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2006)

Abraham Baldwin Agricultural College Associate of Science - AS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

Northwest Florida State College Associate of Arts - AA, General Studies